[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pastis is the most popular aperitif in this country. It is made with anise, licorice and additional aromatic plants.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "Switzerland", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1985 blockbuster movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Robert Zemeckis", "incorrect_answers": ["George Lucas", "Stanley Kubrick", "Steven Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What English word is used in linguistics when discussing the issue of the lack of separate terms for blue and green in many languages?", "correct_answer": "Grue", "incorrect_answers": ["Glue", "Bleen", "Breen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is known as the Vienna Hour in a traditional Sicilian wedding reception?", "correct_answer": "Desert course", "incorrect_answers": ["Giving toasts", "Giving wedding gifts", "Cocktail serving"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do male kangaroos fight to win the privilege to fertilize the female?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They push each other.", "They kick each other.", "They hit each other by boxing."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Young Mr. Lincoln was a hit John Ford-directed movie about the fictional early life of Abraham Lincoln. Who starred as Lincoln?", "correct_answer": "Henry Fonda", "incorrect_answers": ["James Stewart", "Humphrey Bogart", "Jame Cagney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these cities did Steven Spielberg NOT live as a child?", "correct_answer": "Burbank, California", "incorrect_answers": ["Haddonfield, New Jersey", "Cincinnati, Ohio", "Phoenix (Scottsdale), Arizona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is the Indian Flying-fox, found in India, Bangladesh, China, and other parts of Asia?", "correct_answer": "Bat", "incorrect_answers": ["Fox", "Squirrel", "Primate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress and dancer appeared in Bon Jovis video Always?", "correct_answer": "Keri Russell", "incorrect_answers": ["Kiersten Dunst", "Katie Holmes", "Claire Danes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the director of the science fiction movie Soylent Green?", "correct_answer": "Richard Fleischer", "incorrect_answers": ["Walter Slezak", "Sidney Pollack", "Orson Welles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The entire hereditary information of an organism held in the Deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA), is defined by which term?", "correct_answer": "genome", "incorrect_answers": ["proteome", "cryptome", "regulome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name Lumbriculus variegatus, or blackworm, refers to a few worm species. In what way do they reproduce?", "correct_answer": "By regeneration", "incorrect_answers": ["By parthenogenesis", "With eggs", "All of these"]}]